<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MARIO challenge on MARIO-MICCAI 2024</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MARIO challenge on MARIO-MICCAI 2024</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Challenge summary</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/example/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/example/summary/</guid>
      <description>Once the challenge has ended. We will showcase the best solution on the website. And include the name and github solution of the winners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🗂️ Data</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/data/</guid>
      <description>Data source(s) characteristics Imaging data was acquired with a Spectralis OCT device (Heidelberg Engineering). B-scan definition was 496x1024 pixels; the number of B-scans per C-scan was patient dependent (typically 49 B- scans). Consecutive examinations were registered using the Spectralis follow-up option. The data was exported in XML+bitmap format using the Spectralis software version 6.9.4.0. Data was collected at the Ophthalmology department of Brest University Hospital (France). All patients are followed-up for monitoring and treatment of vascular AMD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 🔎 Evaluation and Ranking</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/evaluation/</guid>
      <description>For task 1 The following metrics will be used in the leader board for both phase of task 1&#xA;F1-score, Specificity, Rk-correlation coefficient (RkC) For task 2 The following metrics will be used in the leader board for both phase of task 2&#xA;F1-score Specificity Rk-correlation coefficient (RkC) Quadratic weighted Kappa Ranking method(s) Only participants with comprehensive results for the task will appear in the final ranking. In the final ranking, task 2 will be given a higher weight as it is the most challenging and clinically useful task.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1️⃣🎯 Task 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/task1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/task1/</guid>
      <description>TASK 1: Classify evolution between two pairs of 2-D slices from two consecutive 2D OCT acquisitions. The first task focuses on pairs of 2D slices (B-scans) from two consecutive OCT acquisitions. The goal is to classify the evolution between these two slices (before and after), which clinicians typically examine side by side on their screens. For evolution assessment between two consecutives examination (Task 1), the following fo classes are defined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2️⃣🎯 Task 2</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/task2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/task2/</guid>
      <description>TASK 2: Prediction of evolution within 3 mounts of AMD on OCT 2D slices for planning treatment anti-VEGF. The second task focuses on 2D slices level. The goal is to predict the future evolution within 3 months with close monitoring of patients that are enrolled in an anti-VEGF treatments plan. For the prediction of the evolution within 3 months (Task 2), the following fo classes are defined:&#xA;REDUCED: 0 = ELIMINATED: 1 or PERSISTENT_REDUCED: 2 STABLE: 1 = INACTIVE: 0 or PERSISTENT_STABLE: 3 WORSENED: 2 = PERSISTENT_WORSENED: 4 or APPEARED: 6 Like it is illustrated we provide to participants along side with the OCT for each visit an localizers and some clinical data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>📃 Challenge papers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/challenge_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/challenge_paper/</guid>
      <description>Challenge papers To ensure transparency and reproducibility, we require participants to submit a brief method description alongside their final test set results. This description should follow the Springer Lecture Notes in Computer Science (LNCS) format. An Overleaf template is available template to facilitate this process.&#xA;The paper description should focus on the key steps involved in developing your submitted approach. Here are some recommended elements to include:&#xA;Introduction Method Results Link to public code repository </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>👥 Organizers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/organizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/organizer/</guid>
      <description>(Alphabetical order) Team Organizers Technical Alireza Rezaei 1 2&#xA;Gwenolé Quellec 2&#xA;Mathieu Lamard 1 2&#xA;Mostafa El Habib Daho 1 2&#xA;Pierre-Henri Conze 3&#xA;Rachid Zeghlache 1 2&#xA;Medical Anas-Alexis Benyoussef 4&#xA;Béatrice Cochener 1 2 4&#xA;Thomas Monfort 4&#xA;Team Organizers Technical Leila Ryma Lazouni 5 Mohammed El Amine Lazouni 5 Zineb Aziza Elaouaber 5 6 Medical Sofiane Zehar 6&#xA;Karim Boukli Hacene 6&#xA;Univ Bretagne Occidentale, Brest, F-29200 France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🏆 Prizes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/prizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/prizes/</guid>
      <description>The challenges offer the following awards The top ten performing teams will be invited to participate in a challenge paper. The top-5 teams can have up to 5 co-authors each, while the 6th to 10th place teams can have up to 3 co-authors each. In the paper, we will publish a substantial summary of the challenge results. Thank to the initiative of the BASIRA lab and in collaboration with MICCAI PRIME Workshop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>📜 Rules</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/rules/</guid>
      <description>There several policies that participant are required to consider in order to be included in the competition:&#xA;All final submissions should be in the form of docker containers and follow the provided template provided by the organizers to be tested successfully. Only fully automated methods are acceptable for participation in this challenge as the submission is in the form of docker containers. It is not possible to submit manual annotations or interactive methods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preliminary phase</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/clarity/preliminary_phase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/clarity/preliminary_phase/</guid>
      <description>Please follow the instruction that are provided in our github. You can click on the top right github button to access or directly go to this link https://github.com/YouvenZ/MARIO-Challenge-MICCAI-2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final phase</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/clarity/final_phase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/clarity/final_phase/</guid>
      <description>More details on this phase will come soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🗓 Important Dates</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/important_date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/important_date/</guid>
      <description>The following information outlines a proposed timeline for the challenge, subject to adjustments based on the MICCAI 2024 schedule and the organizers&#39; assessment to guarantee the quality of the challenge.&#xA;Registration Period:&#xA;April 1, 2024 - July 10, 2024&#xA;Release of Training and Off-site Validation Data (Without Labels):&#xA;May 2, 2024&#xA;Off-site Result Submission Period:&#xA;May 2, 2024 - July 10, 2024&#xA;Announcement of Finalists:&#xA;July 11, 2024&#xA;Report (6-page Summary) and Docker Container Submission Period (For Finalists):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zefzaf</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/article/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&#39;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&#39;t cover using CSS to style your theme.&#xA;We&#39;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/compose/announcement/</guid>
      <description>Comming soon ! Stay tuned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
